hyrell.com 2017-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Recruiting Software | Hyrell

At Hyrell Online Hiring Systems ("Hyrell") we know you are concerned about your privacy, so we developed this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, and disclose your Personal Information (defined below). The nature of the recruiting business is sharing your information with others. This means we take the information you provide us and make it publicly available to other people in order to fulfill a recruiting need. You control what information is made publicly available, so if you do not want us to make certain information publicly available, please do not include it.

By using Hyrell, you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information you agree that you are consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails, as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Hyrell Terms of Service. If a term is capitalized and not defined in this Privacy Policy, it is defined in the Terms of Service.

To clarify, "Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy, means information about you that is personally identifiable to you, such as your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing; "Non-Personal Information" means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. Non-Personal Information does not enable identification of or contact with, individual persons. Such information can include, age (but not birth date), gender, education and other demographical information.

## How We Collect Information

We receive and store information you give us. When you submit information on this website and related websites linked to this website, we collect whatever information you include.

As you use our Service, we may also passively collect certain information, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, domain names, access times, and operating system. We also use Cookies, clear GIFs, and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URLs) to gather information regarding the date and time of your use of the Service. This type of information is collected to make our Services more useful to you and to help us improve the Site.

An "Internet protocol address" or "IP address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet access provider when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer Internet access provider, your IP address probably varies from session to session. We may track IP addresses solely in conjunction with session cookies to analyze our web page flow.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a web site. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information and do not infiltrate your hard drive to gather confidential information; our cookies are not "spyware".

### How We Use Information

We use your Personal Information to help you fulfill requests of services provided by us. We also use your Personal Information to contact you and provide you with information that may be useful or interesting to you, including newsletters regarding changes and upgrades to the Services as well as promotional e-mails. By using the Site, you agree to receive this information from us. If you do not want us to send you emails or otherwise contact you, you can always opt out of communications by clicking on the unsubscribe links provided when we contact you.

Hyrell's staff may contact you to participate in our surveys, polls and focus groups. Hyrell works with various companies that value your expertise and your opinion. If you are not interested you can opt out by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided.

From time-to-time, we may create Non-Personal Information from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name and other contact information) that would personally identify you. Generally, we use this Non-Personal Information in statistical analysis to help us analyze patterns in the use of our Services. We reserve the right to use and disclose Non-Personal Information in our discretion.

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site may contain links to other sites. Hyrell is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites other than those sites used in the fulfillment of a service offered by this website.  
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to the Hyrell website and information collected by Hyrell.

### Disclosure of Information

We will disclose your Personal Information to employers who have postings for job openings. We do not control how employers use or disclose information they obtain from us, including Personal Information, and those employers may also share your Personal Information with other employers that may have job openings. Also, if you have come to our Site by following a link from one of our affiliates or business partners or by following a link in an online job posting from a potential employer, they may use the information consistent with their privacy policy instead of this Privacy Policy. Since we do not control how they may use your information, we encourage you to read their privacy policies if available. In addition, we may disclose your Personal Information to third parties with whom we have a co-branding or promotional relationship, including other job sites and our third party support provider. If you would like to opt-out from having your information shared with third party marketing partners, either click on the unsubscribe link provided when we contact you or send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#05767075756a7771454d7c776069692b666a68) asking to be removed from future third party marketing communications.

In addition, we may disclose your Personal Information: (a) if such disclosure is made to comply with the law or an order issued by a court or an authorized administrative agency, respond to a subpoena, legal process, warrant, court order or to protect the rights or property of Hyrell or its affiliated companies, prevent a crime, or protect the personal safety or rights of others; b) to our service providers for the purpose of providing services on our behalf, such as customer service (help), credit card processing, information technology services, and hosting services (including third parties providing services to our service providers); (c) as part of a merger or consolidation, or part of the sale of all or substantially all the stock or assets of the business to which the information pertains; and  
(d) as part of a disposition in a bankruptcy proceeding in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court.

When you voluntarily display or distribute Personal Information on the Site or in other ways, that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. We cannot be responsible for Personal Information you voluntarily display, disclose or distribute on the Site or in any other way.

We will share some or all of your Personal Information with our Affiliates, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

### How to Limit the Ability of Others to See Your Information

Your information you provide to us may reveal your identity. It is up to you to make sure you are comfortable with the information you provide. Hyrell does not have any obligation to modify: (1) potentially identifying information in your application, or (2) your resume to remove or mask information that may identify you.

### Employers Use of Your Disclosed Application

Hyrell does not have any control over how a user of this Site uses and discloses your Personal Information, including information you provide directly to that user. You acknowledge and agree that (1) Hyrell does not evaluate any employer's privacy practices, and (2) Hyrell will not have any liability for any actions of any employer.

### Security

Hyrell is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We have implemented proper controls for and limit access to, and render unreadable prior to discarding, all records containing card account number. In particular, all credit card transactions on our site are conducted using SSL encryption. We have also taken precautions to ensure that our server and electronic systems are secure from breach or intrusion by unauthorized third parties. Lastly, our agreements with service providers (such as hosting providers, credit card processors) contain security and privacy obligations. Even though we have taken steps to ensure that your Personal Information is not intercepted, accessed, used, or disclosed by unauthorized persons, you should know that we are not able to fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information. You assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site and the information you post or access through the Site.

### User Feedback

If you provide feedback, any such comments and any email we receive becomes the property of Hyrell. We may use feedback for marketing purposes or to add to or modify our Services without paying any royalties or other compensation to you.

### Changes

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any material changes to it, we will either alert you via e-mail or post an alert on our home page. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Service. Continued use of our Service following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. All such changes will apply to previously collected information.

### Contact

If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please visit our Community Area at: Support.Hyrell.com  
Thank you for using Hyrell!
